easydate.biz 2015-04-14

# Privacy - Castle Street Investments

## (‘We’) Castle Street Investments plc are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

We are the data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the ‘Act’).

## What information do we collect about you?

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site castlestreetinvestments.com (the ‘Site’) (including your personal details, contact details, mobile phone number and other information you choose to provide to us when contacting us). We may also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions.
  * Your location according to the IP address assigned to your PC by your Internet Service Provider.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Website usage information is also collected using cookies (see below under ‘Cookies’).

## How will we use the information about you?

We use the information we hold about you in the following ways:

  * To notify you of news, updates or announcements related to Castle Street Investments plc, its financial and investor information which we believe may be of interest to you.
  * To help us improve the structure, layout and usability of the Site.
  * To help personalise your repeat visits to the Site.
  * To answer any questions you may raise or respond to any comments you may send to us.
  * To notify you about changes to our service or the functionality of the Site.
  * To carry out market analysis and research.
  * To ensure that we comply with our statutory and regulatory obligations.

## Disclosure of your information

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, the information we have collected about you will generally be one of the transferred business assets. Also in the unlikely event that we or our assets are purchased, your information will also be one of the transferred assets. We may share information about you with:

  * Other companies in the same corporate group as us.
  * A buyer or prospective buyer of our business.
  * Our professional advisers, such as our lawyers, where it is necessary for them to advise us.
  * Other persons if we are under a duty to disclose or share your information in order to comply with any legal obligation.

We may also share information about you with third parties that we engage to help us in certain areas, such as processing payments for services you order from us. However, we will control and be responsible for the use of your information by these third parties.

We may also provide information about you to other users of the Site as reasonably required in order to provide the services that you order from us.

## Marketing

We would like to send you information about goods and services offered by us and selected third parties that we think may be of interest to you. For that, the email address or mobile phone number you have provided can be used. You can also ask us to not to use your personal information, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, by e-mailing us at: [unsubscribe@castlestreetinvestments.com](mailto:unsubscribe@castlestreetinvestments.com)

## Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve the Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise the Site according to your individual interests.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To recognise you when you return to the Site.

For further information about cookies visit: [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above website tells you how to do that. However, in a few cases some of the features on our Site may not function as a result. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Site.

## Where we store your personal data

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a location outside the European Economic Area (‘EEA’). It may also be processed by staff located outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers (for example, staff who are involved in providing services that you order from us, processing your payment details or providing support services for the Site). By submitting your personal data to us through the Site, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password or user ID code which enables you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping the password or user ID code confidential. We ask you not to share a password or user ID code with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Other Websites

The Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Access to information and correction

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us at [info@castlestreetinvestments.com](mailto:info@castlestreetinvestments.com). Please note that we may make a small charge for this service.

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You can ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate at any time by e-mailing us at [info@castlestreetinvestments.com](mailto:info@castlestreetinvestments.com).

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will post any changes to it on this page. We encourage you to regularly review our privacy policy to make sure you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we may share it with other parties.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy then please contact us at [info@castlestreetinvestments.com](mailto:info@castlestreetinvestments.com).
